<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HackTuesApp</string>
    <string name="what_is_cybersec">    Cybersecurity is the protection of internet-connected systems such as hardware, software and data from cyberthreats. The practice is used by individuals and enterprises to protect against unauthorized access to data centers and other computerized systems.

    A strong cybersecurity strategy can provide a good security posture against malicious attacks designed to access, alter, delete, destroy or extort an organization's or user's systems and sensitive data. Cybersecurity is also instrumental in preventing attacks that aim to disable or disrupt a system's or device's operations.
    </string>

    <string name="why_is_cybersec_important">   With an increasing number of users, devices and programs in the modern enterprise, combined with the increased deluge of data -- much of which is sensitive or confidential -- the importance of cybersecurity continues to grow. The growing volume and sophistication of cyber attackers and attack techniques compound the problem even further.
    </string>

    <string name="benefits_of_cybersec">The benefits of implementing and maintaining cybersecurity practices include:

- Business protection against cyberattacks and data breaches.

- Protection for data and networks.

- Prevention of unauthorized user access.

- Improved recovery time after a breach.

- Protection for end users and endpoint devices.

- Regulatory compliance.

- Business continuity.

- Improved confidence in the company's reputation and trust for developers, partners, customers, stakeholders and employees.
    </string>

    <string name="why_use_our_app">Our app is a useful tool which helps users to combat common threats. We combine 2 features - a site safety checker and a password generator/saver. This makes it perfect for people who don't want to download a lot of apps. The site safety feature makes it possible to ensure that browsing sites doesn't compromise your data and security. It tells you if the site is dangerous or not and why it is unsafe to access it. The password generator and saver is a crutial feature to have because using the same password on two or more websites increases the chances of your accounts being stolen. That's why you should use it - to ensure your data is going to be safe. Also the password generator makes it possible to save as much passwords as possible which doesn't only help you stay safe but also doesn't make you remember all of your information which is easy to forget. </string>

</resources>
